My purse brother my purse
baby my purse
[laughs]
I am here brother
I know baby you told me only
but tell these two also so that they
both get convinced
[laughs] baby
baby you told me
[laughs]
Papa quickly leave the house and run away.
But what happened?
Sister is coming to tie Rakhi.
Hey, sister is coming to tie Rakhi, so
what is there to run away from?  Give me ₹1 or
₹200.   Is
aunt also coming?
Oh my god.
Hi.  Lock the house and run away.
Robbers are coming to the house.  [laughter]
Look, my friend has bought a new car.
Ok.  After sitting in it, do
not do anything as if it is our daughter.  Ok.
okay brother.   Do
n't sit brother, I am coming.
Hey, sit with me brother.   Whether
I sit or not,
friend, you sit.  Come on [laughs]
what's this button for?
Hey
[laughter]
lower it down
how much is it brother?
But wait a second
[laughter]
Hey brother, yes tell me where am I in
front of me, hey I don't mean where are you?   In
front of you.
Hey brother, how should I tell you now?  I mean,
where are we both?  face to face.
[laughter]
Tell me where does this road lead?  This
road leads nowhere.  You have to go yourself.
[laughter]
Hey brother, I mean, I want to go to Kathmandu,
Nepal.
Hey brother, please go then.  If you keep telling everyone like this,
when will you reach?
[laughter]
Brother, go,
go quickly, Kathmandu is very bad from here
and listen, don't ask anyone from here,
go quickly, bye, here you go
brother,
hey madam, I don't want it,
why don't I want it, aren't you a beggar? Yes
madam, I am a beggar,
why am I not taking money,
look madam, it's lunch time, come after an hour
[laughter]
You beggars also have lunch time,
yes madam, everyone has lunch time, what do you think, it's
my job only
[laughter]
yes, tell me what happened?
Nothing sir, you were looking for a maid brother, so
I came for that.
Yes, I told you, what all do you do?
Hey sir, I will sweep, mop
and even dust your house.
Correct.  How much will you take?
₹2,000.
₹2,000?  It's too much.
Why is it too much, sir?  All the
maids are charging ₹2,000.
What happened sir?  How much is she saying?   She is
saying ₹2000.
What sir?  Where is ₹2000?  Remove it.  I will do it
for ₹1000.
Yes, okay, okay.  Come on.
Hey hey sir, I was just joking.  Neither
will I take 2000 nor will I take 1500 nor will I
take 1000.  She will do the work directly for ₹500.   Please
go, sister.  Why are you kicking me in the stomach
?   That's a
great thing.  Come on.
Come on sir.
So he must be a very mean man.
Sir, please raise your legs.
And wait for now.  The climax is yet to come.
Brother, I am going shopping.  You
deposit the money in the account.  Bhaiya
Bhaiya
sa ji, who is this?  This is my sister.
Sister
[laughs]
Papa will come after drinking some water.
Drink water, brother
[laughs] No
one should know that we are
coming to the restaurant for the first time.
You have come for the first time.  We did not come.  Ok.
We keep coming.
Why is it not opening what are
you doing don't go there [laughs]
hey move back I will open it okay the door
opens like this [laughs]
hey move aside then let me sit let me sit
wow friend the sofa is so nice wow [laughs]
so nice look at that spoon no problem I will take it
home
sir I have not come to study.  We have come to eat food.
Hey ma'am, this is the food ordering menu.
Please order after seeing this.
Okay, fine sir, I understand.
Sir, what is this ₹10?
Okay, this is a water bottle ma'am.
So, is it spicy or sweet to eat
?  [laughter]
Oh brother, leave it.  Bring the mineral sticks for a minute.   I have
given you a very thin roti, friend
[laughs]
no, I have
given you a very thin roti, friend [laughs]
[laughs]
brother, when mobile is not allowed at the petrol pump, then why the
online facility, when you
knew that she will cheat you, then why did you love her
?  [laughter]
Oh, madam, leave it.  Where will you go?
Malvi Nagar to Mansarovar Mansarovar to Malvi
Nagar.  And this bus will just go away.  So he
said you will go.
Hey, I will take it with me.
Hey, who are you to take the bread?
Hey friend, I am a conductor.  But the bus is
driven by the driver, isn't it?
Oh [laughs] yes didi, only the driver will take it.  He
is my brother.  He is my brother.  You sit down, friend.
You sit.  Hey, why did you lie?   I made a
mistake.  Please forgive me.  Now
sit down.  Now sit down.  Come.  Do you also travel in this bus
?
Hey, I am a conductor so I will come in this bus only.   I
will go, right?  So who books your ticket?
Hey, I'm the conductor.  Who
will book my ticket?
Why?  Don't you travel in this bus?
Oh, yes sister.  I travel in this bus only.
Good?  You show me the ticket.
Mother Goddess, tell me where will you go?  I have to
go to my home.  Come sit, come sit.  Hey, move away.
I have brought my scooter.
[laughs] It's a
wonderful weather, Bhabhi.  Do one thing,
make some tea for me.  Stop the sugar and
hit the leaf.  Get up.
I am your servant sitting here.  Sister-in-law,
make tea.  The weather is getting nicer.  You
cannot explain anything to him.  I will do all the work.
Hey, how long will you insult your brother?  He has grown so big.
You can't do even a few things yourself.   Go and
make tea yourself.  I have the papers of my share of
land.  Sign it quickly.  Should I
also add ginger and cardamom to the tea?   Should I
also give you salty biscuits along with it?
No, no, no.  I will only eat Meerut's mushrooms and
Nankhatai biscuits.
That is not the case.
Wait, you make tea, I will bring it from Meerut.
[laughter]
[music]
Run and reach there, so that we don't go.
Sitting on the stick, I got my ass kicked
[laughs] then he took me away, hey, let's
sit back
[laughs]
one second
Arman Bhai, will we go to the market, tell me will we go or
not?
Hey, why are you not saying anything?  Hey
Armaan,
hey Armaan, give me the password of the hotspot.   I need to
update my mobile.
Why is brother not speaking?
Hey brother, open it and take ₹10.
Brother, it
opened.  Passwords are from one to eight.
Hey, tell me what happened?
Hey, say something, friend.  We will know only if he tells us.  Should I
call?
We don't talk to dogs.
[laughs] It will be
fun, right?
Where are you from brother?   From right
here in the neighborhood behind?
How much is this gutkha?
Of ₹20.
And how long have you been eating?
It's been about 15-20 years.
Hey brother, if you had saved this gutkha money
for 15-20 years, you too would have had a
similar car.  It is a fact.
Hey brother, that car is mine.
What is the matter, sir.  What is the matter, sir.
[laughter]
Clean it properly.
Father.
Hey my son, you have come back from school.
Yes, Papa has come.  Papa, tell me one thing,
why is 15th August celebrated?  What happened on
15th August?
Son, 15th August is celebrated because
our country got independence on 15th August.
Hey dad, why are you lying?  You are still a
slave to your mother.
[laughter]
[music]
Brother, will you give me 500 rupees in cash?
Come on madam, I will give it to you.
Yellow.  [MUSIC] Here you go,
madam.
1 2 3 4 5 By the way brother, tell me one thing.
How much profit did you get from this money?
Hey madam, what will I gain
by exchanging money?
No brother, don't lie.  The shopkeeper is a man.   A
shopkeeper never works without profit
?  Hey madam, if you feel like this then
take your 500 rupee note and
give me my money back.
Hey brother, why are you angry?   The
shopkeeper is a man.  You have such a big shop.
Its rent also has to be paid, electricity
bill also has to be paid.  Earn brother, earn.
Earn it comfortably [laughs].
I can't abuse.  Don't abuse,
look at family.
Run, we are old drivers.  Run it at 80.   The
thread went on and the villagers were watching the ass being
torn.  Sit down, oh my god, oh my god [laughs] friend,
now sitting like this will not work brother,
we will have to either find a good job or do some
good business,
how long will we work if we sit unemployed like this [music]
oh bastard Gaurav Bhai is doing this, yes yes yes
Gaurav Bhai, how are you,
oh brother, we are very good,
tell me how are you, oh
what about us brother, we are
sitting unemployed like this, looking for something,
looking for a job.  Okay, leave all this.
Tell me what's going on these days?
Hey, these days you have opened a hotel at a very
good location.
Hey brother, it's great, you must be printing money like that.
Oh yes brother, I get Rs 10-15 lakhs per month.
Okay, it will be less by 10-15 lakhs brother.
Come, come sometime.  You guys also come here to visit.
Hey brother, listen for sure brother.  We make
plans.  I will plan and inform you in advance
that yes, I am coming on this day.  Ok.
okay brother.
Hey, you have made a great restaurant.  He is looking completely natural, completely
dressed up, wait wait, I will
call him, he will surprise me here and I will be
completely hooked there
[Music]
Hello
Bhaiya, I smiled completely, don't do this my love, give me
one Fevicol, yes the
machine box is behind it, I forgot this, it will be
fun now,
you will have to play the game.   Here you go
brother, is this empty carton of any use to you
?  Sometimes it works and sometimes it doesn't.
Man, I needed this.  Please give it to me.
How much is it?   It is
worth ₹300.   The
machine itself will cost Rs 2-3000.  I will give you ₹300.
Okay bring it.   I will make it Rs
300 for you.   Done.
Okay brother.  Hey brother, yes let me check inside it.  Is there
any stuff?
Bring it here.  Bring it here.
[laughter]
Oh, my friend.
What if we do [laughter]?
What did he say?
Look, my friend has brought the car ahead.   Do
n't do anything while sitting in the car
that will insult me.
Hey, I will not do anything brother.  Ambulatory.
And how is your brother?   Easy Going.
How are you?
We are also fine.
Where should I go for a walk?
Hey, look where you go.  Go to mobile.
Oh brother,
okay brother, let's go.  Ok.
Okay
brother, you sit in the back with my brother.
Yes, the back will be fine too.
[laughter]
[laughter] Hands off.  Are you sitting in the tempo?
Hey, put your feet down brother.  He is sitting in the car.
[sound of throat clearing]
Brother, remove your hand.  Have to turn the glass up.
Hey brother, stop here, stop your hand, stop brother.  Hand-
clap, stop, stop.  What goes there,
Betty?  [laughter]
Hey, how much money are you giving me on loan?
Full ₹500.
Take it, it's 500 rupees.
Hey, this is only 400.
Okay, bring it and show me, now you are gone son.
Hey, this is only 300.
[Music]
Hey, what's that, a note fell here.
Hey, a note fell here.  Take the full 500.
Hello Kajal.
Why did you deposit ₹10,000 in my bank by mistake?  Are
you burnt?
Yes, then what is it?
Yesterday I went to eat Golgappa without telling anyone.
Your burn?
Yes, then what will happen from here also?
Tomorrow I am going to visit my Babu's gallery.   That's
it, it burned.
Looks like a star thief.
Oh my god.
No.
Such a great personality in 2050,
shirt worth 1200, jeans worth 3300, slippers worth 1400, we
roam around with such a nice car,
we are thieves [laughs] brother in
law, don't you people feel ashamed, we are going to have an iPhone, have come to in-laws for the first time and you are giving us water in a steel glass, see brother, we are all going to Manali,
spend ₹10 on each, send it to my account, why
brother, why should we send you money,
brother,
I will bear the expenses of food and room, sell it, okay, I will
send it, okay,
brother, did you see,
yes it has come,
mine has also come, see,
yes it has come, the
message,
brother, after deducting the EMI of the car, 28500,
hey [laughs]
wait, be patient
brother, please give me a glass of sugarcane juice,
madam, should I give you this one or should I make a new one,
ah, give me this one,
madam, should I give it in a glass glass or a paper
glass?
Give it in a paper glass.  Okay, should I give it with ice
or without ice?
Give it without ice.
Okay, should I add lemon or give it without lemon?
Give me the one without lemon.   I will give it right now.
And wait for now.  The climax is yet to come.
Yellow.
Crazy
[encouraging voice]
Hey, it will be fun.
But what is this guy doing here?
How much is it?
Your ₹20?   Should I give it
now or tomorrow?
Hey, give it to me today itself, madam.  Should I give you change or notes
?   Give me a
note.   Should I
pay online or in cash?
Hey, give me the cash, madam.   Should I give you
two for Rs 10 each or one for Rs 20?
Hey, give me one for Rs 20.   Should I
give you the green Rs 20 note or the red note?
Hey, give me the green one.   The
green one?  Should I give it like this or like that?  [laughter]
Oh, give it anyway.  Bring two, friend.
Take it and put it like this.  [laughter]
[laughter]
Where are you coming from so late at night?
Hey, I went to get medicine for Papa.   That
means you went to get medicine for that old man at midnight.
But I have been asking you for the last four days to bring me
vegetables.  Sometimes I am
making lentils.  Sometimes I am making Khichdi.
You are not bringing the vegetables.  Go and
become a slave of that old man.
And wait for now.  [coughing sound]
[laughter]
Take the medicine, father.  Hey, you have come now.  I had given
you medicine 1 hour ago.  If his wife
orders a movie at 12:00 in the night, he will
run and bring it like a dog in 5 minutes.  And she is
bringing father's medicine in an hour.  The bastard is his
wife's slave.
Look at it brother.  This is what happens to us boys.   By becoming like the
pallu of the wife.   Am.   Wait a minute.
Friend, be patient.
Babu, I cannot live without you.
Babu Babu, don't leave me Babu.  Babu, hit me.
Hey, revive me.  Revive de marne bhai revive
de revive de [laughter]
Bhaiya
bhaiya please stop it come on come on
oh brother
[laughter] that's it
uncle what happened
cheat give it to me
take this [music]
take this hey bastard from where did you steal this
money?   Yes
?   Is
n't it a girl?  They are mine.   Tell the
truth.
Yes, they are mine.
Yours?
Yes.
Go, it's equal.  Come on, get out.
evened out?
Yes.  [MUSIC]
Where did the money go?  Who did you give it to?  Yes.  Come on, where did you get it from
?
Come on, tell me.  Tell me where did you get it from?   Did you get it
from here?
Hey madam, I knew you brought this money
by stealing.  That's why I kept the money.
Well,
how much money was there?
Go, it's equal.  Chal
[screaming sound]
[laughter]
Never mind Dhanush.
What is the boy's name?
Everyone was shocked.
Hey, tell me the boy's name.  You will have to chant his name.  Only then will
his soul find peace.
Om Hari Om Mangalam Lord Vishnu to the soul of Dhanush,
yes what did you say hey dog ​​how dare you
oh my god you
took my name
brother how many times my
brother you have 1250 [laughs]
oh brother brother brother got it done you have only 50.
[laughter]
Explain it to your wife.  If she said one to him, she would
say two to me.
Okay, try saying it in front of me.  Hey, are you listening
?  Come here.
Brother.
Mom has come, tell me now.   Let's look at
one or
two.  [laughter]
Oh, I felt so dizzy.
Hey Babu, I am not talking about anyone
except you.  Yes, they should do it.  Okay, fine.
He doesn't agree.  Hey brother, it's a phone worth Rs 1 lakh.   The
second one hit here.
[laughs] The
mehndi looks really nice on your hands.
I have been calling you for so long.
Why are you not picking my calls?  I
also visited you at your home.
What are you doing here?
Who is this boy?
I don't know who this is?
Well, you don't know.  Why are you lying to me
?  Who is this boy?
Hey, I really don't know who this is?
Hey who is this?  He is hitting you with his rapta.
Hey brother, this is my boyfriend.  You
tell me who you are?
I am a delivery boy.  I have brought your
parcel.
[laughs]
You haven't been answering calls for so long.
Yellow.
Hey brother, it has made my cheek red because of you.  I
saw that he had brought the parcel.
Sorry baby sorry.  What did you chase away?   Wait a minute.
Took water.
What's the matter?  Today I am doing a great service.
Hey, I don't need any service.  I am thinking that you must be feeling
thirsty.   You are
not hiding anything.  Tell me quickly what
is the matter?
Hey Mone, I fall in love with a girl and
want to marry her.
Said?
Oh my god.
Why didn't I kill him by poisoning him before you said all this?
Hey, what if you put it in the glass?
Who is it?  Installment one.
Wait sir, I am coming in 5 minutes.
How long it will take?   I am coming
sir.  I am coming.  [MUSIC]
How much longer will it take?   I am coming sir.
Hey, how much more time will you
take?
Wait sir, I am coming in two minutes.
[laughter]
Oh, we cook biscuits, don't lose
biscuits
[screaming sound]
brother.  [laughs]
Hey brother, will you promote the shop?
So you're an influencer?  Yes, I
am an influencer.
Okay, do it, do the collaboration then.   Yes yes I will do it.
By the way, how many followers do
you have?   Is
this about 9 lakhs?
How many?
₹9 lakh.
So guys these are our brothers.  They make very good
videos.  Please like, follow,
share and comment on these.   Go
back and follow back brother, follow back brother.
Sir, we have come to survey unmarried boys.
Yes, then do it.
Sir, will you marry a black girl or a white
girl?
Good?
I will do it with a black girl.
Sir, why so?
Because we know our place.
[Laughter]
Look brother, this great product has been launched in the market just yesterday.
One second
mobile is one number.
Well,
what is its rate?
₹35,000.
Good.  Hey Saurav Bhai, you?
Yes friend, what are you doing here?   He had
come to buy the mobile.
Well, the mobile is great.  By the way, you are my
friend.  You will have to charge a good rate.
You will get 400 rupees [music].
I think
this is my fault too.
I am a brother, brother.   So
guys, today's video
ends here.  Tell us in the comments which
clip or video you found the
funniest.  Rest I searched for a lot of funny clips in this video
which
takes a lot of hard work.  So friend, if you liked it then
like the video, subscribe to the channel
and
you will keep getting to see similar videos on our channel.
So let's meet again new